wapspell.com 2018-03-08

# Privacy Policy

Friends, Downloads, Info - mobile!

 **Introduction**  
wapSPELL is a mobile social networking site and service to provide easy platform to share information and to communicate.

This page covers stuff related to wapSPELL and its services.

We do not allow or recommend our services to be used by minors below the age of 13 years.

**Parental involvement** : We strongly recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet and we encourage parents to teach their children about safe internet use practices. Materials to help parents talk to their children about safe internet use can be found on this help page.

**User Information**  
When you sign up for wapSPELL services you provide us with your name, email, gender and birth date. More personal information may be entered in association with user accounts to be displayed in user profiles and search processes solely by users' own consent. Moreover, there can be certain information which would be required to be filled in in special cases for security and authentication reasons.

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with wapSPELL under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help wapSPELL communicate with you about offers from wapSPELL and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of wapSPELL's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.   
We transfer information about you if wapSPELL is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, wapSPELL will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

wapSPELL displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria�for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.   
wapSPELL does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. wapSPELL advertisers include major advertisement networks and other direct advertising companies.

We may also use your email address for communication which will be provided to us by your consent.

wapSPELL stores cookies (small pieces of information) on your browser/device.

wapSPELL may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your wapSPELL account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

[[HOME]](https://web.archive.org/)
